Contact

Flat-7A, House-11, Road-12, Lake View Society, Badda, Dhaka-1212, Bangladesh. 8801789270125 (Mobile) golammostofa31188@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ golammostofa89 (LinkedIn) iedcr.gov.bd (Company) github.com/mostofa62 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
CSE

Languages

English

Certifications

React - The Complete Guide SQL and PostgreSQL: The Complete Developer's Guide Microservices with Node JS and React

Golam Mostofa

Programmer at IEDCR

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Summary

I have been working as a software engineer for more then 7 years. my skills involved JavaScript, jQuery, Vue Js, React Js, Node js, PHP, Laravel Framework, WordPress, Java, Spring Boot, Python, MySQL, Mongo and PostgreSQL Database.

Experience

Institute of Epidemiology, Disease Control and Research IT & Programming Officer
August 2019 - Present (4 years)

Mohakhali, Dhaka 1212

- 1. Surveillance Based Questionnaire Data Collection and Analysis Application System Development using jQuery, PHP, Laravel Framework , MySQL.
- 2. Web Based Application Development using using Vue Js, Java ,PHP, Laravel Framework , MySQL.
- 3 .Background Processing Task Automation using PHP, Python, Java, Postgresql.
- 4. CHAMPS Bangladesh Website development and Data Visualization using WinterCMS (based on Laravel Framework) and Vue js and React js with Apex Chart.

Maestro Solutions Ltd.
Software Engineer

February 2019 - July 2019 (6 months)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

- 1. Web application development using PHP, Laravel Framework, Java, Spring, Spring Boot, MySQL, Oracle, Angular JS.
- 2. Desktop Application development using C#, SQL Server Database Engine.
- 3. Fingerprint Based Application integration using C++ & C#

Golden Ispat Limited
Programmer
November 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 3 months)

recombon 2017 Gardany 2010 (1 year o m

Chattogram, Chattogram, Bangladesh

- 1. Web application development using PHP, Laravel Framework, MySQL
- 2. Desktop Application development using C#, SQL Server Database Engine.
- 3. Hosting and maintaining website and different web application.
- 4. IP addressing, sub net masking and how to configure routers, wireless router, switches, firewalls, network printers and other related network device to setup office network
- 5. Quick troubleshooting for any kind of hardware and software related issues

Denim Expert Ltd.

Assistant Programmer

February 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 9 months)

Plot No: 96-100 Sector 3 Karnaphuli EPZ North Patenga Chittagong-4204

- 1. Web based application development using PHP, MySQL, Yii1 and Yii2 PHP Framework
- 2. Hosting and maintaining website and different web application
- 3. IP addressing, sub net masking and how to configure routers, wireless router, switches, firewalls, network printers and other related network device to setup office network
- 4. Quick troubleshooting for any kind of hardware and software related issues

Walletmix Limited

Software Engineer

October 2013 - February 2016 (2 years 5 months)

House- 2/B, Road- 8, , Nikunja- 2, Khilkhet, Dhaka 1229

- 1. Web based payment processing application portal development using PHP, MySQL, Yii1 and Yii2 PHP Framework
- 2. Bank certificates installation and integration for Payment Gateways provided by Bank
- 3. Payment Gateway Extension development for CMS like woo-commerce, open-cart, magento, prestashop.

Education

Islamic University

Master of Engineering - MEng, Computer Science · (November 2019 - December 2020)

University of Information Technology & Sciences (UITS) Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology (2008 - 2013)